It was going to be time in this part of the video to do that
day 9
I had 1 idea Man?
And I really believe that this may work,
but for that I need to find the right tools to be able to do this business.
Oh now yes
girl sits.
Rita is here to go straight to pass.
She's going to be just Caião.
Why don't you play on Google I like to connect with people.
That's not connection man.
This is 1 exercise I prefer to do to be more creative.
Let's go this is we're worth it
there's no reason the things I want to make my ideas never have in places.
Dude is awesome.
It's further forward.
He gave a certain hand.
In life there is 1 thing called investment return Dude so
from New EU I will invest in my idea to be able to run.
There is no way EU can put this idea out.
If I don't invest in it.
That's it bro.
I'm taking the bus and tomorrow we're going to see what I'm going to do.
Worth
Hey hey.